Guide to the Standard Bible Committee Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Presentation and Evaluation, Series V
  - Magazine articles
    - "Gleanings from the Greek New Testament" by Ralph Earle ( Preacher's Magazine ), 1946 Jul-Aug (Box 12, Folder 220)
    - "RSV Users on the Increase" by P.C. Landers ( National Council Outlook ), 1956 Mar (Box 12, Folder 221)
    - "The Story of a Bible" by Bennett Cerf ( Saturday Review ), 1956 Jul 7 (Box 12, Folder 221)
    - "Which Bible for You?" by John Haverstick ( Saturday Review ), 1956 Nov 10 (Box 12, Folder 221)
    - "The RSV Committee at Northfield" by Luther Weigle ( Northfield Schools Bulletin ), 1957 Jul (Box 12, Folder 221)
    - "Is This Book Blasphemous?" by A. Clay Sicher ( Christian Herald ), 1953 (Box 12, Folder 220A)
  - Newspaper clippings
    - 1944-1952 May 1944-1952 May (Box 12, Folder 222)
    - 1952 Sep 1952 Sep (Box 12, Folder 223)
    - 1952 Oct-1953,1957, 1973,n.d. 1952 Oct-1953,1957, 1973,n.d. (Box 12, Folder 224)
  - Pamphlets
    - "An Introduction to the Revised Standard Version of the New Testament", 1946 (Box 12, Folder 225)
    - "Translating the Bible for Today" by Dr. C.T. Craig, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 225)
    - "An Introduction to the Revised Standard Version of the Old Testament", 1952 (Box 12, Folder 225)
    - "The New Bible: Why Christians Should Not Accept It" by Carl McIntire, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 225)
    - "A Criticism of the Revised Standard Version 1952 of the Bible" by Bob Jones, Jr. (Box 12, Folder 225)
    - "The Revised Standard Version - A Travesty" by J. H. Cohn, 1952 (Box 12, Folder 226)
    - "The New Blasphemous Bible", 1953 (Box 12, Folder 226)
    - "Which Version? A Critical Evaluation of the RSV by the Faculty of Grace Theological Seminary", 1953 (Box 12, Folder 226)
    - "The Revised Standard Version as Seen By a Southern Baptist," by A. L. Goodrich, D.D., 1953 (Box 12, Folder 226A)
    - "The Revised Standard Version: A Sermon" by W.E. Dowell (Box 12, Folder 226)
    - "The Eye Opener," by J. J. Ray, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 226A)
    - "Bible Marker for Ministers, Teachers, Bible Students of the Evangelical United Brethren Church", n.d. (Box 12, Folder 226A)
    - "Do We Have the True Bible?" by Rev. Armin C. Oldsen, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 226B)
    - "Isaiah 7:14 - 'Young Woman' or 'Virgin'?" by William Sanford LaSor, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 226B)
    - "The Revised Standard Version: A Genuine Joy" by Clovis C. Chappell (Box 12, Folder 226B)
    - "Whose Unclean Fingers Have Been Tampering With the Holy Bible?" by David Otis Fuller, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 226C)
    - "An Open Letter Concerning the Revised Standard Version of the Bible", 1954 (Box 12, Folder 226C)
    - "How Do They Understand the Bible" by Arthur F. Katt, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 226C)
  - Miscellaneous manuscripts and correspondence
    - "The New Revision and its Acceptance" by Raymond P. Morris (Box 12, Folder 227)
    - "A History of the Work of the RSV Committee Since 1952", n.d. (Box 12, Folder 227)
    - "Brief History of the Work of the American Bible Revision Comm.", n.d. (Box 12, Folder 227)
    - Corr. re. The New Bible: Pro and Con Lecture bulletin, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 227)
    - "The Revised Standard Version of the Bible," by Luther A. Weigle (Box 12, Folder 226)
    - "The Authorization and Use of the Revised Standard Version of the Bible", 1957 (Box 12, Folder 226)
  - Publicity material, news releases
    - 1946,1952,1959 1946,1952,1959 (Box 12, Folder 228)
  - Commemorative material
    - 1952 1952 (Box 12, Folder 229)